<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DadgumMediaGroup]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DadgumMediaGroup]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 14:40:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[William Blanco: Creator, Producer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>William Blanco: Creator, Producer</h1><p>What began as a high school internship for the ABC network’s Latin America Bureau in Miami, FL, became a life-long adventure for William Blanco. After the internship, he accepted a position with the ABC network as sound engineer, covering the news in devastated and war-torn regions across Latin America and the U.S. From there Blanco went on to become a producer for World News Tonight; cameraman for COPS pilot production and subsequent seasons; Operations Manager for ITV a small syndicated network; Director, Producer, and Editor of dozens of commercials and music videos for high profile artists as Supervisor of Television Productions for South Beach Film and Television; and an avid freelancer traveling to over 40 countries.

Blanco has seen it all (and done it all) in the world of multimedia television and visual arts. His intense passion for communicating powerful messages from the lens for over 30 years has brought him where he is today producing riveting stories to capture hearts through reality television. Blanco lives with his beloved wife in Fort Pierce – the treasure coast of Florida. When Blanco is not working in television, he enjoys developing websites, maintaining his e-commerce business, teaching teens how to produce videos as an outreach, and spending time with his family.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d51ffabe-e54e-420f-9cce-1aa703e1b7e8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://spark.adobe.com/page/4fQjt/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7bd84814-985b-42c3-b2e0-669ef1add606</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 14:39:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>